thumbplay.com 2010-12-31

# Download | Thumbplay Music

Effective May 27, 2010

We at Thumbplay, Inc. ("Thumbplay") understand that you value your privacy and we strive to respect that privacy when you are using our services. This Privacy Policy describes what information we gather from you, how we use that information and what we do to protect it. By using the Thumbplay website, you are expressly consenting to the information handling practices described in this policy.

## Information We Collect From You

When you sign up with Thumbplay, you establish a password-protected personal account for ordering ringtones and downloading services such as graphics, games and other items or participating in the Share feature ("the Services"). During the account creation process and/or to place an order, we may request certain contact and billing information (such as your name, a valid email address and your cell phone number). We use this information to provide you with our Services and to contact you about the items in which you have expressed interest.

When you create a Thumbplay account, we keep track of your interactions with us, including but not limited to your site activity, order history, payment history and correspondence. We do this to provide you with better service, for billing and administrative functions, to improve your customer experience and for internal research and reporting purposes.

## Online Account Profiles

We may request information from you through optional online account profiles, surveys or contests. Participation in these profiles, surveys or contests is completely voluntary and you have a choice whether or not to disclose this information. Information requested may include contact information (such as your mailing address), and demographic information (such as your zip code or education level). By submitting this information, you enable us to provide you a more personalized Thumbplay experience.

Please note that information you provide in an optional public profile can be viewed by anyone, and can potentially be used to contact you or send you unsolicited messages. If you use a bulletin board, blog or chat room on our site, you should be aware that any personally identifiable information you submit there can be read, collected, or used by other users of these forums, and could be used to send you unsolicited messages. We also permit customers to upload their photos to our web site using our "Share" service. We are not responsible for the personally identifiable information you choose to submit in these forums.

We post customer comments on our web site which may contain personally identifiable information such as the customer's name. We do obtain the customer's consent prior to posting the comment to post their name along with their comment.

## Emails and SMS Messages

By registering for a Thumbplay account, you agree that we may send you the following types of email communications: welcome emails, our weekly newsletter, account status updates and promotional content. You may opt-out of receiving our email newsletter via the unsubscribe links in each email. You can also opt-out of specific types of email communications through your Account Settings.

Our Services feature the distribution of content to your cellular phone, and by registering for a Thumbplay account, you agree to receive SMS messages to your phone, including messages regarding Services you request, account status updates, and occasional SMS newsletters. You will also have the opportunity to opt-in and receive surveys and promotional content by our affiliates. You may opt out of our SMS newsletter by sending an email to [un@thumbplay.com](mailto:un@thumbplay.com) or by responding to the SMS newsletter indicating that you would like to unsubscribe.

Our website provides you with the opportunity to refer your friends, family members or relatives to the Thumbplay Services. For this feature of our website to work, we need to collect your friends and families' email addresses. The email addresses we collect in this context are not used for any other purpose other than to send a one-time referral.

## Technical Information

The Thumbplay website collects and retain technical information regarding visits to the Thumbplay website such as the IP address assigned to the computer visiting the site, the type of browser used by a visitor and the operating system running the user's connections to the service. This data is not linked to your personal account. It is used to analyze the ways in which our site is used, and how we can improve the user experience.

## How We Use Your Information

Thumbplay uses your personal information in the following general ways: To provide you with our Services, to allow for your identification and authentication onto the Thumbplay website, for billing and administrative functions, to contact you, and for internal research and reporting purposes. We also use the information optionally provided by you in surveys for purposes of monitoring or improving the use and satisfaction of the Thumbplay Service. Third parties who provide website support services, billing, processing, fulfillment, marketing, and other services on our behalf may also access your personal information to provide those services.

We may send you website and service announcement updates with important information about the service through the email address or cell phone number you provide. We may also notify you about special Thumbplay-specific promotions available through our trusted partners. You can opt-out of receiving these promotional emails, but not service related messages, at any time either through the unsubscribe link in the email we send you, or by visiting our opt-out page at <http://www.thumbplay.com/go/unsub-email>.

We may also share anonymized information — information that does not identify you — with third parties such as advertisers.

## Information Relating to Children

Thumbplay Services are intended for users age 18 and up. By registering for a Thumbplay account or providing information on other parts of the Thumbplay site, you represent that you are 18 years of age or older. We will not knowingly collect personal information of children under 18 years of age, and if we learn that we have inadvertently collected such information, we will promptly delete it.

## Viewing and Updating Your Account Information

If your personal information changes, or if you want to update your email preferences, or if you want to cancel the Thumbplay Service, you may update your profile by visiting the Account Settings section of our Web site. You must be signed in to access your Account Settings. You can also email our Customer Support at [music.support@thumbplay.com](mailto:music.support@thumbplay.com) or contact us by telephone or postal mail at the contact information listed below.

## Cookies

Thumbplay uses cookies in order to manage your individual visits to the Thumbplay website. Cookies are also used to determine how you were referred to the Thumbplay website, as well as your browsing and buying activities, to assist us with marketing and product development. You must enable cookies to use the Thumbplay Service.

Thumbplay allows other companies that display advertisements on our website to set and access their own cookies on your computer. Use of cookies by other companies is subject to those companies' own privacy policies, not this policy. Advertisers and other companies do not have access to Thumbplay's cookies.

## Disclosure of Personal Information to Third Parties

We do not rent or share your personal information with non-affiliated third parties except to provide products and services you have requested, when we have permission, or as described in this policy, including under the following circumstances.

\- when we believe in good faith that it is necessary to respond to subpoenas, court orders, or other legal process, or to exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims;

\- when we believe in good faith it is necessary in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of our terms and conditions, or as otherwise required by law.

Finally, we may transfer information, including any personally identifiable information, in the event Thumbplay is acquired by or merged with another company.

## Third Party Sites Appearing on the Thumbplay Site

The Thumbplay website contains links to and advertisements for sites operated by third parties whose policies regarding the handling of personal information may differ from ours. While we endeavor to associate only with reputable websites, Thumbplay cannot be responsible for the information handling practices of these other websites. Any information you provide on those sites is subject to their privacy policies, and not this policy.

## Co-branding

Thumbplay maintains co-branding relationships with various service providers who include our promotional offers either directly on their websites or through inline links on their websites. When you sign up with Thumbplay through one of these websites, you establish a password-protected personal account for ordering Thumbplay ringtones, graphics, games and other items and services. During the account creation process and/or to place an order, we request, through that partner, the same contact and billing information that we ask of users who sign up directly on our website (such as name, a valid email address and cell phone number). You must agree to the Thumbplay Terms and Conditions posted to these websites in order to register. The Thumbplay privacy policy applies only to personal information collected on these websites for the purpose of Thumbplay registration.

## Protecting your information

Thumbplay takes reasonable measures to safeguard your personal information during transmission and when stored on our network. However, due to the open communication nature of the Internet, communications between you and the website, and the website and you, may not be secure, depending on the network you are using to communicate with us.

If Thumbplay learns of a security breach through which sensitive personal information may have been compromised, we may notify you electronically so that you can take appropriate protective steps. By using this web site, or providing personal information to us through any means, you agree that we can communicate with you electronically regarding security, privacy, and administrative issues relating to your use of this site.

If you have any questions about security on our web site, you can contact us at [music.support@thumbplay.com](mailto:music.support@thumbplay.com.com).

## Referral Program

Our Referral Program allows you to easily tell your friends and family about Thumbplay. When you use the Program, we will ask you for you and your friend's name, phone number and/or email address. We will enable you to send your friend a one-time email or SMS message inviting him or her to visit Thumbplay, and the contact information you provide for this purpose will not be maintained by Thumbplay after your message is sent.

Thumbplay uses third party service providers to administer the Referral Program. The personal information collected and stored through the Referral Program is only used for the operation and ongoing maintenance of the Referral Program and will not be used for any other purposes or disclosed to any third parties other than those service providers that help administer the Program. If you use our Referral Program to download your address book information from your web based email account, we will immediately delete any account information that you have provided us once the download is complete.

You and your friends may opt-out of participation in the Referral Program at any time via opt-out links in all Referral Program communications or by sending an email to [friends_support@thumbplay.com](mailto:friends_support@thumbplay.com) or visiting <http://www.thumbplay.com/go/unsub-email>.

## International Visitors

Thumbplay is hosted in the United States and complies with United States laws, including privacy and data protection laws. At this time, Thumbplay's services are not available to visitors from outside the United States.

## TRUSTe Privacy Program

Thumbplay, Inc. is a licensee of the TRUSTe Privacy Program. TRUSTe is an independent, organization whose mission is to build user's trust and confidence in the Internet by promoting the use of fair information practices. This privacy statement covers the website. Because this website wants to demonstrate its commitment to your privacy, it has agreed to disclose its information practices and have its privacy practices reviewed for compliance by TRUSTe.

The Watchdog Dispute Resolution link required in the privacy statement is [http://watchdog.truste.com/pvr.php?page=complaint&url=http://thumbplay.com](http://watchdog.truste.com/pvr.php?page=complaint&url=http://thumbplay.com)

The following websites are covered under this policy: http://www.thumbplay.com and all sub-domains thereof.

## Changes to this Privacy Policy

As we update and expand our Services, we reserve the right to modify this privacy policy at any time. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here, by email, or by means of a notice on our home page. By continuing to use the site after changes to this policy, you agree to those changes.
